Hey everyone, it's me Celine!
It's going to be another Paradise video
because I have so many Paradise pants by now
and so many colors.
I decided to do only one colored outfits today.
To be honest, I couldn't think of a good story behind it
or a good title.
So, one colored outfits with my Paradise pants.
Let's go!
Starting with the first color.
Alright.
The red outfit. It's the only one with the jacket
It is a lot
Do I think it's too much? Yeah, I do
Would I wear it out? No, I wouldn't. Is it fun? Yes
The bodysuit is from Paradise which is kind of a cheat because I actually wanted to do this without
other Paradise products for the next outfits then and yeah, I bought a jacket secondhand
I had the boots already. This is just like red PVC overkill. I kind of see myself
with it in winter though because I also have these pants in the thermal version
the warm version and the jacket is really warm actually. I never liked this kind of
puffy jackets I don't know but I think with this look like way too much it's kind of fun.
Also the length is really perfect with the pants here.
I'm a fan, surprisingly. Well, who knew?
All right, on to the next outfit.
all right this is the all white outfit I realized that white looks really good with the blue hair
as a lot of colors do but yeah I'm really sad about this because normally I love to wear black
but I already did take pictures with this top and I have to say it's so cute I mean the cut
and the fit the puffy sleeves I would love to have it in black to like wear it in my regular
daily life where I wear black and not white but yeah I think this is a really cute outfit all in
all let me check yeah cute I would like I would like to have some frilly lacy white accessories
for that like a kind of lazy choker and white something like that I think that
would be really cute together all right next color
green next and I have to say I failed with the shoes because I do not have
shoes in green at all and not even especially not in this kind of metallic
green but have a look at the bodysuit and the leggings it's the exact shade of metallic green
I managed to find a matching bodysuit and I have to say it was by coincidence
I have the metallic green pants for a long time now and I ordered this bodysuit at Fashion Nova
also a long time ago I did never use it so far I completely forgot about it to be honest and then
And a few weeks back I was like, wait, does this match? Is this the exact same color?
Then I ran into the store and dug out the leggings and the bodysuit and ta-da!
Completely the same.
Bonus points for that because, let me just...
Because it's not even that easy to find the exact same colors.
But okay, it's just the leggings and the bodysuit, so let's do the next outfit.
it's all pink and I yeah it's not the same shade of pink I admit that do you know how hard it is
to find the exact same shades of colors when you're looking online shopping online and don't
know what actual color it is and how it light and the photograph whatever anyway this is the closest
that I could find. The top is from Fashion Nova, the Paradise pants and my
trusty GRO heels, whichever I dig out when I need pink heels, which is quite
often actually. It's definitely very pink if I would have had this... It's definitely
very pink if I would have had this outfit last year when the Barbie movie
was released I maybe would have worn this to the cinema or not. Okay for the
last outfit I'm going to do a real experiment I have no idea how it will
look let's see.
All right this is game over. I am defeated. I didn't try these combinations on before so this yeah this is the total fail now.
I have these pants and I thought the bodysuit could be a match but it isn't
and also I do not have any nude shoes or light brown shoes so I thought well my
skin looks like this color anyway alright I hope you really enjoyed this
video I had a lot of fun doing this I think it was hilarious and yeah just a
bit of having a laugh and digging out some really really old paradise pants I
haven't been wearing in the past anyway tell me in the comments which one was
your favorite leave a thumbs up here check out my patreon for behind the
scenes and subscribe to this channel all of it you know the drill I will see you
in the next video if you want to see some serious paradise pants videos I
have several here on my channel also with black pants there are a lot of black
pants so check them out and see you next time bye